GOOD MORNING EVERYONE!
I AM __________________ AND I AM ______________. WE  ARE YOUR HOSTS OF THE DAY.
WELCOME TO ____________________.EVERYTHING NEW IS EXCITING FOR HUMAN-KIND. 
IT IS FULL OF EXCITMENT AND EXCUBREANCE. A LOT OF SURPRISE, CHEERFULNESS, AND 
JOY. TO THE FACES WITH HOPE, POSITIVENESS, AND PASSION, I WELCOME ALL OF YOU INTO OUR WONDERFUL FRESHERS DAY!
THIS DAY, WE WELCOME OUR  BATCH OF NEW FACES INTO THIS PRESTIGIOUS COLLEGE WITH FUN, COLOURS AND A LOT OF GAMES.
ONCE AGAIN WECOME EVERYONE!
LET US OFFER OUR SINCERE REVERENCE TO THE LIGHT THAT BESTOWS LIFE, PROSPERITY AND ACCOMPLISHMENT,
THAT SYMBOLIZES THE INFINTITE AND THE PURE. LET US PRAY TO BE FREED FROM
THE MISERIES THAT OUR OMIISIONS AND COMMISIONS BRING. LET US NOW LIGHT THE HOLY LAMP. 
MAY I REQUEST PRINCIPAL MAAM AND THE TEACHERS TO DO THE HONOUR.

AFTER LIGHTING OF THE LAMP AND AFTER THE SARASWATI VANDANA.

THANK YOU TEACHERS, WE REQUEST YOU TO KINDLY TAKE YOUR SEATS.


Namashkaar,shashtriyakal, adaab, assalam vaalekum janaab.
mai hun ____________ aur mai hun__________________
Apke sundar se mukhde pe jo do kan ke tukde aur natural camera hai, unhe tikaye rakhiyega, 
kyunki agar najare hati toh samjhaye dhurghatna ghati,
aur yaha par dhurghatna ye hai ki you will miss a chik chik bhoomm fireee performance. 
So ladies and gentlemen boys and girls put your hand toghter for our first performance of the day..
deje wale babu gana bajaya jayee.
WHAT A PERFORMANCE IT WAS!
TALLIYAN  BAJTI REHNI CHAHIYE...
THAMM JAIYE THAMM JAIYE 
ARZZ KIYA HAI..
WAHHH WAHH
ARZZ KIYA HAI 
WAHHH WAHHH
ARZZ KIYA HAI
AREEE SAHIBAAN MEEHRBAAN KADARDAAN AB KARDO HM PAI EK EHSAAN AUR KARO JO ARZZ KARNA HAI...
HN TOHHH ARZ KIYA HAI...

जो गर चलना हो साथ, तो अपना हाथ बढ़ा दीजिये…
हो गर मन में प्रेम तो फिर मुस्कुरा दीजिये|
है आज हमारा, क्या पता कल हो ना हो….
कोई गीत हो मन में तो फिर गुनगुना दीजिये|

WAHHH WAHHH
GEET SE YAAD AYA BHT DINO SE GHARWALI GANO KI DUN SUNAYI DE RAHI HAI TOH KYU NA UNHI KO STAGE MAI BULAYA JAYE
SO LET US CALL UPON OUR GHARWALI SINGERS ON THE STAGE WITH THEIR MESMERIZING VOICES.

SO HOW WAS IT?
SUPER SE BHI UPR SE BHI UPR KA PERFORMANCE. ISN'T ?

-mai tumse kuch puchu?!
-hn jarur
-tumhara fav clr kya hai
-are ye kaun puchta hai yr
-ok so 25698 + 34567 * 89765%89997 kitna hota hai
-pink hai mera fav. colour
lol phle hi bata diya hota toh thodi izzat bacch zati! accha chalo fir batao pink city kaun si hai
-mujhe nhi pata
-toh audience se puchte hain
--jaipur
aur jaipur kiski capital hai
--rajasthan
aur rajashtan kiske liye famous hai
--apne dance ke liyee
so put your hands together for our rajasthani dancers

-
arz kiya hai
-no wahh wahh
-kya mtlb
-are ab sab kuch tum hi hi arz kr doge ka kisi aur ko bhi mauka doge
-kaun hai yha zo meri baraabari kr skta hai?!
-tumhari barabri lyk toh koi nhi but hn tumse bht accha jarur hai
so lets call himanshu on the stage 
tallliyan bajaooo....

wahh wahh 
wahh wahh
ALL WORK AND NO PLAY MAKES A JACK A DULL BOY.
AND ofcourse a jill a dull girl.
and we are sure no one wants to be dull on such a bright day.
so lets have some fun, lets have some games.
so our first game is
intro
rules
start
end

-kehte hai bacche ka sabse pehla school uska ghr hota hai
-aur sbse phle guru use mata peeta
-qnki sbse phle vohi hme ungli pakde chalna seekhate hn
-ungli pakdke tune chlna sikhaya na dahkleej unchi hai ye paar kara do baba mai teri malika
-are are kya ho kya hai ye tumhe kin bhavnao mai beh gye
-oh tumhe nhi pata hmara next performance hai ye
oh really?! toh unhe sunte hn na tumhe nhi
so put ur hands together for our next performance



Don’t stop make it pop,

DJ, Blow my speakers up.

Tonight, I am a fight,

Till we see the sunlight,

Tick tock on the clock,

But the party doesn’t stop,
So please welcome Abhishek on the stage for Hip Hop


Most of us are gharwali over here and we do love  rap music, hip-hop, bollywood etc etc but kuch bhi keh lo jaan toh humari hmare gharwal mai hi basti hai.
all the gharwali out here put your hands up and say we love our ghrwal.. and with this we present before you all gharwali ki jaan maan aur shaan gharwali dance.


Continue reading at Anchoring Speech Script for Song Performance in English, Hindi, Marathi | TeenAtHeart

 अगली performance आने से पहले मैं यह कहना चाहूंगा कि अगला डांस जिस गाने में है, वह गाना गढ़वाल में ही नहीं बल्कि गढ़वाल से बाहर भी बहुत famous
 हुआ है और सबसे ज्यादा famous जिस platform में हुआ है, वह है India's National Mobile App - Tik Tok मे...
KOI GUESS KAREGA KONSA SONG HAI

.
तो अब हम पढ़ते हैं अगले performance की तरफ जो है एक गढ़वाली Grouop Dance...




Let’s move forward to a different dance form that shouts of sophistication and grace. 
It is time for a semi-classical dance act, a dance form which is a combination of classical and Bollywood.
 Our next performance is on the beats of..ghr more pardeshiya

THANK YOU ..... FOR THE WONDERFUL PERFORMANCE








-CHALO EK CHOTA SA GAME KHELTE HAI
-KAISA GAME
-MAI TUMHE EK SONG KI ENGLISH LYRICS BATAUNGI AUR TUMHE GUESS KRNA HAI KONSA SONG HAI
-LO YE BHI KOI GAME HAI MAI CHUTIKIYON MAI BATA DUNGA/DUNGI
-OK OK SO LETS START:-It’s the night of dance, 
                     foget everything else,
		     This is the season of love,
                     Now come to me, and stay here,
		     Prem niya mausam chhe
-YE KYA VICHITR SI BALA HAI MUJHE NHI PATA
-TO AUDIENCE SE PUCHTE HN
--YES IT IS CHOGADA TARA
:-Ho aaavi gayi 
  mann bhulo bhaddi baat,
  Prem niya mausam chhe,
  Ab aao mere paas, reh jao mere saath,
  Prem niya mausam chhe,

SO NOW I WELCOME OUR DANCE TROUPE WHO IS GONING TO PERFORM ON THE BEATS OF CHOGARA TARA

so what next guys?
how about a majedaar dance performance?
why not?!
isi baat pai arzz kiya 
मन मचल के मौर होना चाहिए,
इस शानदार se din में थोडा शोर होना चाहिए….
दिखाने को तो हम din भर डांस दिखाए आपको,
मगर आपकी तालियों में भी थोडा ज़ोर होना चाहिए!

तो शानदार se din में आप सभी को Entertain करने का दौर चल चूका है, और इसी दौर को आगे बढ़ाते हुए….
इस धमाकेदार डांस के बाद, अब देसी गर्ल्स की है बारी…
पर वो तब ही आएंगी, जब बजेंगी तालियाँ ढेर सारी!
So please put your hands together, for our Desi GirlS who is going to dance on the beats of............




NOW THATS WHAT I CALL A FEAST TO THE EYES.


 